aarki.com 2018-06-29

# Privacy Policy | Aarki

#### About our services

Aarki is a mobile advertising company that provides mobile application developers, brands, and advertising agencies (our "Customers") with a platform and service to deliver advertising to users on their mobile devices ("end Users"). In order to best deliver advertising to these end Users, we collect and may use certain information about these end Users to target the most relevant advertising. 

#### What does this privacy policy cover

Aarki, Inc. ("Aarki") is committed to respecting the privacy rights of its Customers, visitors, and other users of the website located at www.aarki.com (the " **Site** ") or of any software or services provided by Aarki (collectively, the " **Service** ") and end Users that may be served advertising by Aarki in mobile applications and sites by Aarki on behalf of our Customers. Below is a summary of the personally identifiable information (" **Personal Data** ") and other information that is collected from or about Customers, visitors and other users of the Service and our policy regarding the use and disclosure of that Personal Data, and the measures we take to safeguard that Personal Data. 

This Policy is only applicable to the Service, and not to any other third party websites or services that you may be able to access from the Site, each of which may have data collection and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Policy. This Policy also explains how you can contact us if you have a question about, or want to exercise any of, your legal rights in respect of any of your Personal Data that Aarki may be processing. 

We will only collect and use Personal Data in accordance with applicable data privacy law, in particular where: 

  * we have lawful grounds to do so, including to comply with our legal obligations;
  * we are performing a contract with you for our Services; and
  * we have legitimate interests in using your Personal Data and your interests and fundamental rights do not override those interests.

For the purposes of the EU General Data Protection Regulation ((EU) 2016/679) (" **GDPR** "), we are "data controller" in respect of Personal Data that we collect and use for the purposes of providing the Service. In certain cases, where we are carrying out services on behalf of our Customers, we also act as "data processor". 

This policy is effective as of May 15, 2018. 

#### Customer Policies

As part of the Service we offer to our Customers, we may collect Personal Data as well as process Customer-provided end User data for the purposes of carrying out our Service. This section shall cover policies related to both of these areas. 

### INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES

_INFORMATION COLLECTED BY AARKI_. In operating the Site and providing the Service, Aarki may collect certain information, including without limitation the following: 

  * _PERSONAL INFORMATION_. When you register for the Service, Aarki may ask you for Personal Data including but not limited to your name, business name, business address, phone number, e-mail address, contact preferences, and billing information. We use this Personal Data to remain in contact with you about your use of Aarki Services and for the purposes of billing. We may retain your Personal Data after you cease to use Aarki Services for our accounting and business records. 
  * _AUTOMATICALLY COLLECTED INFORMATION_. 
    1. Our servers automatically recognize information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website, which may include information such as the domain names and Internet Protocol (IP) addresses of visitors to the Site, as well as the browser type and the date and time of the browser’s access to the Site. No Personal Data about you is revealed in this process and we generally treat information collected by such process as non-personal data. However, to the extent that Internet Protocol (IP) addresses or similar identifiers are considered Personal Data by applicable law, we treat these identifiers as Personal Data. 
    2. The Site may also gather anonymous "traffic data" that does not personally identify you, but that may be helpful for marketing purposes or for improving the services we offer. 
    3. Aarki uses services to capture session usage of some areas of the site to assist with Customer troubleshooting and learn about Customer usage of the Site to help us make decisions about product improvements. Session captures are limited to select areas of the Aarki site only and do not record any other browser or computer activity. As part of session information we collect account, IP, and browser and operating system data. We do not capture any password inputs. 
  * _COMMUNICATIONS_. When you send email or other communications to Aarki, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. 
  * _RETENTION OF INFORMATION_. Aarki will retain your Personal Data for as long as necessary to fulfill the purpose(s) for which it was collected and to comply with applicable laws. We review the Personal Data we hold at regular intervals and delete permanently or anonymise any Personal Data which is no longer necessary. 
  * _USE AND SHARING OF INFORMATION_
    1. _PERSONAL INFORMATION_. We will not sell, distribute or rent your Personal Data with any third parties without your consent, except to our trusted business partners for the purpose of providing you with, and operating and maintaining, the Site and Service, to comply with applicable law or as otherwise specified herein. We may use your Personal Data and/or share it with certain third parties to activate and maintain your account, verify your identity, check your qualifications, or follow up or resolve with transactions or queries initiated on the Site, including, but not limited to, processing your credit card payment or other payment, if applicable. Please note that we have appropriate data privacy safeguards in place with our third party business partners with whom we share your Personal Data and who are providing services or functions on our behalf. We may also use your contact information to inform you of any changes to the Site or Service, respond to your questions, inquiries, comments and instructions, take good faith steps to enforce the terms of use with respect to the Site and Service, maintain the security and integrity of the Site and Service or our systems, or to send you additional information about Aarki.
    2. _ANONYMOUS INFORMATION_. We use anonymous information to analyze our Site traffic, but we do not examine this information for Personal Data. In addition, we may (subject to "AUTOMATICALLY COLLECTED INFORMATION" above) use anonymous IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers, to administer our Site, or to display the content according to your preferences. Traffic and transaction information may also be shared with business partners and advertisers on an aggregate and anonymous basis.
    3. _USE OF COOKIES_. We may use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, or for other purposes, such as to help us to understand user behavior, and learn which areas of the Site are useful and which areas need improvement. We treat information collected by these site analytics cookies as non-Personal Data. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings on your browser. However, if you choose to disable this function, your experience at the Site may be diminished and some features may not work as they were intended. You can also delete cookies that have already been set. You may wish to visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) which contains comprehensive information on how to do this on a wide variety of desktop browsers.
    4. To opt-out of our mailing list, please click unsubscribe in the body of the email communication

### WEBSITE AREAS BEYOND AARKI’S CONTROL

_PUBLIC FORUMS_. The Site may include interactive forums such as bulletin boards and blogs. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your Personal Data. Aarki will not be liable for any disclosure of your Personal Data or other information as a result of your use of any such public forums, that you display publicly or that becomes publicly known as a result of your actions. 

_THIRD PARTY WEBSITES_. The Site may contain links to other websites. If you choose to visit any other websites other than the Site, we will not be responsible for the privacy practices or content of those other websites, and you shall bear all risk of access to such websites. It is solely your responsibility to review the privacy and usage policies at those websites and confirm that you understand and agree with their policies. 

### USE AND SHARING OF CUSTOMER PROVIDED INFORMATION FOR AARKI SERVICES

A Customer may provide Aarki with information about end Users for the purposes of advertising to those end Users through Aarki services. This information is passed to Aarki via the Customer, either directly or through a technology partner of the Customer. The Customer is responsible for requesting permission to use personal data from end Users for such purposes. 

_WHAT DATA WE RECEIVE_ , We receive mobile device advertising identifiers, such as Android GAID and iOS IDFA. We do not receive or store any other Personal Data on end Users from our Customers. 

_HOW WE USE THIS DATA_. When buying media on behalf of our Customers, if we are able to buy an advertising opportunity (Impression) that matches a mobile advertising identifier of one of our Customer’s end Users we may show that end User an ad from that Customer. Not all impressions served to an end User on one of our Customer end User lists may be targeted for that end User. The end User may be served advertising from Aarki that is not specifically targeted to their mobile advertising identifier. 

### END USERS

Our technology and how we collect information on end Users. End Users are those that may be served advertising from Aarki on behalf of our Customers. 

In providing services to our Customers, we collect information to identify end Users’ interests and activity in mobile applications. We use this information to determine what advertising we think may be most relevant to an end User to serve them the most relevant ad opportunity from our Customers. To identify end Users we use mobile device advertising identifiers, such as Android GAID and iOS IDFA, and IP information. The information we collect on end Users is provided via the mobile app or site owner to Aarki via technology partners we are integrated with that enable the buying and selling of advertising opportunities, such as banners and videos. 

In addition, some of our Customers may utilize the Aarki platform to engage in re-targeting or re-engagement activities. Retargeting and re-engagement is when an advertiser (our Customer) wants to advertise to an end User that may already be using, have used, or expressed interest in their product or service. Our Customers, in their relationship with this end User/s may request and collect some personal identifier and then may provide this information to Aarki in order to retarget or re-engage the end User. The Customer will provide a mobile device advertising identifier only, such as an Android GAID or iOS IDFA to Aarki for the about consumers they are interested in reaching via advertising and the Customer is responsible for obtaining consent to use personal identifying information from the end User before providing to Aarki. As an end User you can manage the use of your device identifier for such activity by reaching out directly to the advertiser, our Customer. You can also opt out of all targeted Aarki advertising as outlined below. 

_OPTING-OUT AND OPTING-IN_. Aarki may use non-Personal Data that we collect in mobile apps to tailor advertising to you in other mobile apps and sites. You can opt out of cross-app and cross-site use of non-Personal Data in general by: 

  * For iOS devices, you can opt out of targeted advertising by updating to iOS 6.0 or higher and enabling "Limit Ad Tracking" setting. On iOS 6 this setting is located in Settings -> General -> About -> Advertising menu. On iOS 7+, it is located in Settings -> Privacy -> Advertising menu.
  * For Android devices, you can "Opt out of Ads Personalization". To opt out or to find your advertising identifier go to Settings -> Accounts -> Ads.

If you would like to opt out of targeted advertising from Aarki please enter your device advertising identifier. Please note, you may still be served general, non targeted advertising from Aarki. 

### SECURITY

Aarki has implemented and maintains administrative, technical and physical security measures to help prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, loss, theft, misuse, destruction and alteration of Personal Data, Customer provided end User information, but we cannot guarantee that such measures will prevent any unauthorized access, disclosure, loss, theft, misuse, destruction or alteration of Personal Data or Customer end User information. Aarki will notify affected parties of any suspected or confirmed unauthorized access, disclosure, loss, theft, misuse, destruction or alteration of your Personal Data or Customer end User information to the extent required by and in accordance with applicable state and federal laws. We may attempt to notify you so that you can take appropriate protective steps, or we may post a notice on the Site if a security breach occurs. 

### DISCLOSURE AND SALE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

_LEGAL DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION_. Without limitation to the foregoing, we may disclose Personal Data if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce the Terms of Use Agreement, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Aarki, its users or the public as required or permitted by law. 

_SALE OF INFORMATION_. In order to accommodate changes in our business, we may sell, buy or otherwise transfer portions of our company or other companies or assets, including the information collected through this Site. In the event of a proposed or actual purchase, sale (including a liquidation, realization, foreclosure or repossession), lease, merger, amalgamation or any other type of acquisition, disposal, transfer, conveyance or financing of all or substantially all of the assets of Aarki, user information (including Personal Data) will be one of the assets transferred to the transferee. 

### INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA

Our headquarters are located in the United States. Accordingly, if you are an EU citizen/resident in the EU, please note that we may transfer your Personal Data to our data centers located in the United States and Hong Kong, in accordance with EU data protection law requirements. Such a transfer may be necessary in order to perform a contract with you for the Service or to fulfil your requests and/or through obtaining your consent. In other cases, we may use standard contractual clauses that have been approved by the European Commission. 

### YOUR RIGHTS IN RESPECT TO YOUR PERSONAL DATA

If you are an EU citizen and reside in the EU, or are non-EU national residing in the EU, you may have the following rights with respect to the Personal Data you provide to us or we collect from you when you use the Service, to the extent permitted by applicable data protection laws: 

  * To see what Personal Data we hold about you (if any), including why we are holding it and who it could be disclosed to;
  * To have your Personal Data rectified;
  * To have your Personal Data erased if it is no longer necessary for the purposes for which it was processed, you have withdrawn your consent to, or object to, its processing and there is no other legitimate grounds for processing it or you consider it has been unlawfully processed;
  * To have the processing of your Personal Data restricted if you contest its accuracy, its processing is unlawful, we no longer need it but you need it for a legal claim, or you have objected to its processing and await verification of our legitimate grounds for processing it; and
  * To withdraw any consents you have given us to the processing of your Personal Data.

You can exercise these rights at any time by contacting us by email at [privacy@aarki.com](mailto:privacy@aarki.com). You also have the right to complain to your national data protection regulator if you feel that your Personal Data has been unlawfully processed. 

### CONTACT INFORMATION AND POLICY UPDATES

_CONTACTING US_. If you have any questions about this Policy, or our practices related to this Site, please feel to contact us at [privacy@aarki.com](mailto:privacy@aarki.com). 

_UPDATES AND CHANGES_. We reserve the right, at any time and at our sole discretion, to add to, change, update, or modify this Policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on the Site and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site, provided that if you do not wish to accept any such changes, you will be given the option to opt-out of the use of the Site or the receipt of any Services in accordance with the Terms of Use Agreement. It is your responsibility to review this Policy from time to time to ensure that you continue to agree with all of its terms. You agree that, by continuing to use or access the Site or Services following any update or change, you shall be bound by any such update or change.
